Double Edge is a action, thriller, tv movie film directed by Steve Stafford.
In this fast paced action-thriller, daytime's top star Susan Lucci plays two roles: both a crack FBI
agent and the elusive killer-for-hire who she stalks in a deadly game of hide-and-seek.
Each driven by an obsession to succeed, the perfectly matched competitors hurtle full-speed
through a risky game od double-cross to an unexpected and deadly finish line.
Maggie Dutton / Carmen Moore, played by Susan Lucci.
Harry Carter, played by Robert Urich.
Paul, played by Michael Woods.
Webber, played by Kevin Dunn.
Ferese, played by Paul Freeman.
Sister Theresa, played by Kari Lizer.
Double Edge is a 1992 Israeli-American thriller drama film written
and directed by Amos Kollek and starring Faye Dunaway.
The tone is intense.